Guide to the Cornelius W. de Kiewiet papers, 1949-1951.
de Kiewiet, Cornelius W. papers, 1949-1951
- Advisory Committee to the Office of the Dean of Men and Dean of Women., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Veterans Administration Guidance Center., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Office of the University Proctor., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Director of Veterans Education., 1949-50 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  Mover, Donald H.
- Cornell University Library., 1948-51 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  McCarthy, Stephen A.; Emanuel, Victor; Ward, J. Carlton; Wright, Theodore P.; Scheetz, Francis H.; Powell, Whiton.
- Cornell University Library - Vose Gift. Vose, C. R., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Cornell University Library - New Library., 1949-51 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  Wilson, Louis R.; McCarthy, Stephen A.; Wright, Theodore P. Committee on the Library Building.
- University Archives and Collection of Regional History., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  Fox, Edith M.; McCarthy, Stephen A.; Wright, Theodore P. Cornell University Library.
- Cornell University Library - Southwest Stacks., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Committee on the Library Building., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Cornell University Press., 1948-51 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  Comstock Publishing Company.
- University Publications., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  Howes, Raymond F.
- Comstock Publishing Company., 1943-50 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Committees., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Fulbright Scholarship Material and Exchange of Students and Professional Personnel., 1949-51 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Committee to Study the Need for Television., 1948-51 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty., 1949-51 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- United States Dept. of the Navy Request for the Use of Facilities at Cornell University in Case of National Emergency., 1945-49 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Festival for the Contemporary Arts., 1949-51 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  Barnette, Stuart; Daiches, David.
- Committee on Selection of a President., 1949-51 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  Dean, Arthur H.
- Committee to Study Nuclear Studies, Physics, and Chemistry., 1949-51 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  Bethe, Hans A.; Wilson, Robert R.
- Committee to Study Problems of Student Morale., 1949-51 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  Gubb, Larry E.; Passmore, L. Alan; Moyer, Donald H.; Wright, Theodore P.
- Committee on General Education., 1950-51 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Committee on Dishonesty in Examinations., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- WHCU., 1947-51 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Hanna, Michael R. Peabody Foundation.
- Photographic Science Laboratory., 1948-51 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Willard Straight Hall., 1948-51 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Personnel Office., 1946-50 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Committee to Study Policies in Connection with Non-academic Personnel., 1949-50 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Placement Service., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Munschauer, John L.
- Placement Service Budget., 1949-50 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- University Faculty., 1948-51 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Murdoch, Carleton C.
- University Faculty Meetings., 1946-51 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Memorandum on Certain Aspects of Administration in Cornell University., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- University Faculty Publications., 1940-51 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- University Faculty Minutes., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Dean of the University Faculty., 1950-51 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Letters to Various Committees., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Committee on University Policy., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Committee on Military Science and Physical Training., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Committee on University Lectures., 1949-50 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Messenger Lectures.
- Committee on Prizes., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Committee on Student Conduct., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Committee on Student Activities., 1947-50 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Undergraduate Fellowships., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Committee on Scheduling of Public Events. Labor Youth League., 1949-50 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Committee on Calendar., 1949-50 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Committee on Tenure and Efficiency., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Academic freedom.
- Committee to Draft a Faculty Bill of Rights., 1947-49 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Communications Between Administration and Faculty., 1950-51 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Kahn, Alfred E.; Copeland, Morris A.
- Committee on Military Curricula., 1950-51 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Committee on Necrology., 1950-51 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Pensions and Retirement., 1948-51 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Teacher's oath of Allegiance., 1948-49 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Teaching Load and Academic Evaluation., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- University Faculty Committees., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Salaries of Faculty., 1946-51 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Salaries of Faculty., 1947-50 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Committee to Consider Ways and Means of Regularizing and Standardizing the Compensation of Assistants.
- Annual Salary Tabulation., 1948-50 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Faculty Salaries Annual Salary Tabulation., 1946-49 (Box 5, Folder 36-38)
- Appointments of 12 Months and 9 Months, Academic Year., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Sabbatic Leaves., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Cornell University Endowed Chairs., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Faculty Titles, Faculty Instructor., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Faculty Dismissal Procedure., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  Hood, J. Douglas; Wright, Theodore P.; Myers, William I.
- Dept. of Agricultural Economics. DeGraff, Herrell., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Dept. of Entomology., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Rural Science Organization., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  Dept. of Rural Sociology.
- Dept. of Rural Education., 1949-50 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Dept. of Agronomy., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  Bradfield, Richard.
- Forestry., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  Cope, Joshua A.; Swanson, Gustav A. Dept. of Conservation.
- Dept. of Pomology., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Extension Services., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  Simons, L. R.
- Students in the College of Agriculture., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- College of Architecture., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Clarke, Gilmore D.; Day, Edmund Ezra.
- College of Architecture., 1943-51 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  Mackesey, Thomas W.; Clarke, Gilmore D.; Day, Edmund Ezra; Cummings, George Bain; Well, F. M.; Parke, John S.
- College of Arts and Sciences Committee on Educational Policy., 1950-51 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- College of Arts and Sciences Faculty Meeting Minutes., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1946-51 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  Hulse, M. L.; Cottrell, Leonard S.
- College of Arts and Sciences -Departments., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Dept. of Chemistry., 1948-51 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  Wood, Lloyd A.; Debye, Peter J. W.; Cottrell, Leonard S.; Papish, Jacob; Kirkwood, John G.
- Dept. of Classics., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Dept. of Economics., 1948-51 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  Montgomery, Royal E.; Southard, Frank A.; Wilcox, Clair; Copeland, Morris A.; Adams, George P.
- Dept. of English., 1949-51 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  Mizener, Arthur M.; Cottrell, Leonard S.; Mineka, Francis E.; Abrams, Meyer H.; Nungezer, Edwin; Myers, Henry A.
- Epoch Literary Magazine. Hathaway, Baxter L., 1948-49 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Dept. of Far Eastern Studies., 1950-51 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  Fahs, Charles B. Rockefeller Foundation.
- Dept. of Fine Arts., 1948-49 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  Waage, F. O.; Cottrell, Leonard S.; Clarke, Gilmore D.
- Dept. of Geology., 1948-51 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  Cottrell, Leonard S.; Cole, W. Storrs; Harris, G. D. New York State Geological Association; Paleontological Society.
- Dept. of Geology - Repairs to Building., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Cole, W. Storrs; Cottrell, Leonard S. McGraw Hall.
- Dept. of German., 1948-50 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Lange, Victor; Faust, Albert B.
- Dept. of Government., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Rossiter, Clinton L.; Einaudi, Mario; Weiss, Ottocaro; Cella, Paola.
- Dept. of History., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Guerlac, Henry; Gates, Paul W.; Fox, Edward W.; Stern, Fritz; Cottrell, Leonard S.
- History of Science., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Guerlac, Henry.
- Division of Literature., 1948-49 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Daiches, David.
- Dept. of Mathematics., 1950-51 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Kac, Marc; Wolfowitz, Jacob.
- Division of Modern Languages., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Cowan, J. Milton; Albov, Alex; Gibson, Anson W. Russian Language Instruction.
- Dept. of Music., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Brewer, R. Selden; Emerson, Willard I.; Kirkpatrick, John; Falkner, Keith; Winter, George; Campbell, William A.; Grout, Donald J. Chimes.
- Cornell University Bands., 1947-49 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Hull, Robert L.; Kuypers, John M.; Hospital, Ralph.
- Dept. of Philosophy., 1948-50 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Cottrell, Leonard S.; Black, Max; Vlastos, Professor.
- Dept. of Physics., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Wilson, Robert R.; Howe, Harley; Cottrell, Leonard S.; Smith, Lloyd P.; Feynman, Richard P.; Bethe, Hans A.
- Dept. of Psychology., 1947-51 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Moore, A. Ulric; Williams, Robin M.; MacLeod, Robert B.; Liddell, Howard S.; Fuller, Bernice; Dallenbach, Karl M. Cornell Behavior Farm; Social Science Research Center; Division of Psychology (Proposed).
- Dept. of Romance Literature., 1948-50 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Papez, Professor; Bishop, Morris; Day, Edmund Ezra.
- Dept. of Russian Studies., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Szeftel, Marc.
- Dept. of Speech and Drama., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Hulse, M. L.; Wright, Theodore P.; Cottrell, Leonard S.; Parmenter, Richard; Albright, H. Darkes; Woehl, Arthur L. Community theatre.
- Dept. of Sociology and Anthropology., 1947-51 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Kerr, A. E.; Leighton, Alexander H.; Sharp, Lauriston.
- Studies in Culture and Applied Science., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Dept. of Zoology., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Singer, Marcus; Adelmann, Howard B.; Cottrell, Leonard S.; Dalton, Robert H.; Dean, Arthur H.
- Tutorial Program., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Fox, Edward W.
- Committee for Pre-Medical Students., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Hinsey, Joseph C.; Wright, Theodore P.; Henderson, Algo D.; Coxe, Warren W.; Barnes, LeRoy L.
- Campus Organizations and News Outlets., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- College of Engineering., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Hollister, Solomon C.; Wright, Theodore P.; Dean, Arthur H.; Malti, Michel G.; Day, Edmund Ezra. Purdue University.
- School of Mechanical Engineering. Hollister, Solomon C., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- School of Mechanical Engineering -Students., 1950-51 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Vinson, Jack.
- School of Civil Engineering., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Liang, Ta; Hollister, Solomon C.
- School of Electrical Engineering., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Rhodes, Fred H.; Bard, Francis N.
- School of Aeronautical Engineering., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Sears, William R.; Thompson, M. J.
- School of Chemical Engineering., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Carpenter, Walter S.; Olin, Franklin W.
- New York State College of Home Economics., 1949-51 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Vincent, Elizabeth Lee; Walker, Norton Blaine (Mrs. ).
- New York State Veterinary College., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  Hagan, William A. Taiwan Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction.
- College of Engineering Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  Nomicos, Michael; Hollister, Solomon C.; Burrows, Charles R.; Conwell, Walter L.
- Veterinary Virus Research Institute., 1949-50 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  Hagan, William A.; Knowles, Asa S.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Hinsey, Joseph C.; Wright, Theodore P.; Knowles, Asa S. New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board; Society of the New York Hospital.
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board., 1949-51 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  Day, Edmund Ezra; Bayne-Jones, Stanhope; Wilson, Robert R.; Hinsey, Joseph C.
- Sloan-Kettering Institute., 1945-51 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Cornell University Medical College -Discrimination., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  Hinsey, Joseph C.; Wright, Theodore P.; Silver, Edward; Dicker, Edward E.; Hanlon, Lawrence W. American Jewish Congress; Anti-Semitism.
- Law School., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  Stevens, Robert S.; Noyes, Nicholas H.; Peer, Sherman.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  Catherwood, Martin P.; Brosman, W. R.; Hatch, Brainard; Eurich, Alvin C.
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1949-51 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  Dunbar, Virginia M.; Alien, Lucile. Society of the New York Hospital.
- School of Business and Public Administration., 1949-51 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  English, Donald; O'Leary, Paul M.; Stassen, Harold E.; McConnell, James A. G. L. F. Cooperative Exchange, Inc.
- School of Hotel Administration., 1949-51 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  Meek, Howard B.; Vincent, Elizabeth Lee; von Strahl, Otto; Wright, Theodore P. New York State College of Home Economics Dept. of Hotel Administration; Hotel Ezra Cornell.
- Statler Club, Statler Hall., 1950-51 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  Meek, Howard B.; Statler, Alice M.
- School of Education., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  Winsor, A. L.
- School of Education Administrative Board., 1947-51 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Reading Clinic., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  Glock, Marvin D.
- School of Nutrition., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  Maynard, L. A.; Moore, Norman S.; Babcock, Howard E.; Eurich, Alvin C.
- Graduate School., 1948-51 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  Hollister, Solomon C.; Jones, Charles W.; Rhoads, C. P.
- Tuition Waivers., 1949-51 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Heckscher Fund., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  Cottrell, Leonard S.; Gates, Paul W.; Wright, Theodore P.; Jones, Charles W.; Freeman, Harrop A.
- Cornell University Medical College -Discrimination., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Fellowships., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Farr, Newton C.; Gage, Henry Phelps.
- Summer Session. Jones, Charles W., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The State Colleges at Cornell University., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Peterson, Arthur H.; Winsor, A. L. New York State Education Dept.
- Dept. of Military Science and Tactics., 1946-51 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Day, Edmund Ezra; Hospital, Ralph. ROTC.
- Air ROTC., 1946-51 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Ivy League., 1945-51 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Kane, Robert J.; Marcham, Fred G.; Dodds, Harold W. Board on Physical Education and Athletics; Televising of football games; Eastern College Athletic Conference; University of Pennsylvania.
- Budget for Physical Training., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Mackesey, Thomas W.; Wright, Theodore P.; Kane, Robert J.
- Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder S)
  Elsenhower, Milton S.; Kane, Robert J.; Gubb, Larry E.; James, George K.; Dodds, Harold W. Eastern College Athletic Conference; Intercollecgiate Association of Amateur Athletes of America.
- Naval ROTC., 1945-51 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Military Establishment at Cornell University., 1944-51 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  ROTC.
- Newman Laboratory of Nuclear Studies., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Newman, Floyd R.; Kikuchi, Seishi; Wilson, Robert R.; Dodds, Harold W.; Bethe, Hans A.; Cottrell, Leonard S.; DeGraff, Herrell; Wright, Theodore P.; McDaniel, Boyce D.
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1947-51 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Hollister, Solomon C.; Jones, Charles W.; Riparelli, Carlos.
- High Voltage Laboratory., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Myers, William I.; Hollister, Solomon C.; Meigs, Robert B.
- Summer Session., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Stutz, Frederick H.
- Administrative Board of Summer Session., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Carnegie Corporation - Research in Technological Change., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Malott, Deane W.; Gardner, John W.; Wright, Theodore P. Program of Experimental Field Research in Technological Change (Proposed).
- Social Science Research Center., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Williams, Robin M.; Catherwood, Martin P.; Cottrell, Leonard S.; Sharp, Lauriston; Wright, Theodore P.
- Social Science Research Center -Executive Committee., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Lilly Endowment - Social Science Research Center., 1949-50 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Kahn, Alfred E.
- University Testing and Service Bureau., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Clock, Marvin D.; Chauncey, Henry; Cowan, J. Milton; Winsor, A. L.; Woodruff, A. D.
- Infirmary and Clinic., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Moore, Norman S.; Darling, C. Douglas; Dean, Arthur H.; Wightman, Henry B.; Eldredge, Laurence H. Committee on Student Health and Hygiene.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Adams, Arthur S.; Mendenhall, William W.; Upson, Maxwell M. Davella Mills Foundation; Newman Foundation.
- Alumni., 1945-50 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Emerson, Willard I.
- Alumni Fund., 1947-51 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Stevenson, Howard; Gubb, Larry E.; White, Robert W.; Emerson, Willard I.; Murphy, Emmet J.; Bache, Harold L.
- Alumni Office. Brewer, R. Selden; Donlon, Mary H.; Wade, Harry V.; Wright, Theodore P.; Murphy, Emmet J., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- War Alumnus Certificate., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  Morse, John H.; Murdock, Carleton C.; Wright, Theodore P.
- Scholarships., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Committee on Scholarships and Grants-in-Aid., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Murdock, Carleton C.; Williams, Herbert H.
- Committee on National Scholarships., 1947-51 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  Storandt, Robert W.
- President's Tuition Scholarship., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Scholarships, Fellowships, Grants-in-Aid Policies., 1945-51 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- McMullen Scholarships., [1937] 1949 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Chamberlain, Robert F.; McMullen, John; Hollister, Solomon C.; Day, Edmund Ezra.
- Kenneth O. Reed Scholarships., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- College of Engineering Scholarships., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- New York State School of industrial and Labor Relations Scholarships., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  Catherwood, Martin P.
- Sidney Hillman Foundation Scholarships., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Committee on Student Aid., 1949-50 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  Merrill Fund.
- Phi Kappa Psi Foundation Scholarships., 1950-51 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs Scholarships., 1950-51 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Jim Dayton Scholarship., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Gene Batchelor Scholarship., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Spencer L. Adams Scholarship., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Professorship in American Values., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  Willcox, Bertram F.; Fox, Edward W.; Monroney, A. S. Mike; Collyer, John L.; Konvitz, Milton R. American Way of Life Program.
- Lectures on American Way of Life., 1948-49 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  Catherwood, Martin P.; Hoover, Herbert.
- Area Studies., 1948-49 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  Institute of Human Relations.
- Indie Studies., 1948-50 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  Muzumdar, Haridas T.; Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Nehru, Pandit.
- Army Air Force Request for Area Language Instruction., 1948-49 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  Cowan, J. Milton; Williams, Herbert H. Division of Modern Languages.
- Prizes., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Social Science Research Center., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  Williams, Robin M.
- Tests and Testing., 1948-51 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  University Testing Service.
- Tests and Testing., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Cornell Plantations., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Myron Taylor Lectures on International Affairs., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  Churchill, Winston; Einaudi, Mario; Bunche, Ralph J.
- Sigma Xi Lectures., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  Adelmann, Howard B.
- Program for American Studies., 1949-50 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Interdepartmental Committee on Statistics., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Attendance at Classes., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  Synagogue Council of America.
- Scholastic Requirements., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Probation Notices on Transcripts., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- New York State Colleges of Agriculture and Home Economics Dept. of Extension Teaching and Information., 1949-51 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  Ward, William B.
- Meetings Held at Cornell University for Adult Education and Extension., 1949-51 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Proposed Conference at Cornell University by the World Council of Churches., 1949-50 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Irish, Ruth F.; Leiper, Henry S.
- Vacations for Office Staff., 1949-51 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Research Laboratory for Diseases of Dogs., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Center for Integrated Aerial Photographic Studies., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Christensen, Nephi A.
- Guggenheim Aviation Safety Center., 1949-50 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- State University of New York -Administrative Meetings. Eurich, Alvin C., 1949-51 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- State University of New York - Budgets and Finances. Frodin, Reuben; Eurich, Alvin C., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder S)
- State University of New York - Building Program. Wright, Theodore P.; Eurich, Alvin C.; Peterson, Arthur H., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Relocation of the New York State Veterinary College and the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Day, Edmund Ezra; Catherwood, Martin P.; Eurich, Alvin C.; Clarke, Gilmore D.; Hagan, William A.; Babcock, Howard E.; White, Cornelius J.; Parke, John S.; Knowles, Asa S.
- State University of New York - Ceremonies and Exhibits., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Myers, William I.
- State University of New York - Committees and Consulting., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Myers, William I.; Teegen, O. J.; Cowen, P. A.; Vincent, Elizabeth Lee; Galbreath, Malcolm B.; Eurich, Alvin C.; Kelsey, Lincoln D. Committee on Extension Services.
- State University of New York -Legislation., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Myers, William I.; Vincent, Elizabeth Lee; Dean, Arthur H.; Catherwood, Martin P.; Hanna, Michael R.; Day, Edmund Ezra.
- State University of New York - Alvin C. Eurich, Personal., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- State University of New York - Tuition and Fees., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Vincent, Elizabeth Lee.
- State University of New York -Newsletters., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- State University of New York -Organization., 1948-51 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Eurich, Alvin C. Commission on the Need for a State University.
- State University of New York -President's Memo., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Hagan, William A.; Eurich, Alvin C.
- State University of New York -Publications., 1947-51 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- New York State Education Dept., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  Newsom, Carroll V.; Wright, Theodore P.
- New York State Education Dept. - Reports., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  Newsom, Carroll V.; Soper, Wayne W.
- New York State Education Dept. -Mimeographed Letters., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- A Miscellaneous., 1948-51 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Adams, Arthur S. American Institute of Pacific Relations; American Committee on United Europe; American Sovereignty Campaign; Asia Institute.
- Accomodations., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  Hampton Institute.
- American Council on Education., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  Adams, Arthur S.; Zook, George F.
- American Council on Education -Bulletins., 1948-51 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- American Council on Education - Minutes of Meetings., 1949-50 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- American Council of Learned Societies., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  Odegaard, Charles E.
- American Council of Learned Societies Meeting of January 25-27., 1949-51 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- American Council of Learned Societies -Finance Committee., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- American Council of Learned Societies Meeting of 25-27 March 1949., 1948-49 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- American Council of Learned Societies., 1949-51 (Box 8, Folder 32-35)
- American Institute of Pacific Relations., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- American Historical Association., 1948-50 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  Ford, Guy Stanton. Committee on Documentary Reproduction.
- American Institute., 1949-50 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  Peters, H. F. University of Munich.